<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Javier Rodríguez</title><link>https://jrcampo.com/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Javier Rodríguez</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 17:03:28 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jrcampo.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The homemade Pegasus [EN]</title><link>https://jrcampo.com/posts/spyware-post/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 17:03:28 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://jrcampo.com/posts/spyware-post/</guid><description>Introduction 🔍 In the last few months, the growing trend of spyware 1 and the report 2 of socially recognized and famous victims made that the word &amp;ldquo;Pegasus&amp;rdquo; appears in our conversations with friends over coffee or on the front pages of the media.
But, what is Pegasus? Basically, is a spyware that can infiltrate a device and harvest personal and location data, control the phone&amp;rsquo;s microphones and cameras without the user&amp;rsquo;s knowledge or permission.</description></item><item><title>Objetivo conseguido: Ascenso [ES]</title><link>https://jrcampo.com/posts/ascenso-post/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 20:03:28 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://jrcampo.com/posts/ascenso-post/</guid><description>Fantasmas del pasado&amp;hellip; Finales del mes de mayo de 2017, una época donde nuestra máxima preocupación podrían (o deberían) ser las pruebas de de acceso a la universidad, pero durante un tiempo para todos nosotros no fue así. Un equipo junior formado por once jugadores, once personas de las cuales la mayoría llevabamos compartiendo vestuario desde que apenas podíamos con el balón, en definitiva, once amigos.
Tras una temporada increíble en cuanto a resultados, habiéndonos proclamado campeones de liga, nos afrontábamos a la fase de ascenso a Liga Gallega con muchas ganas e ilusión para tratar de conseguir un ascenso histórico para el C.</description></item><item><title>Search automation in Shodan [EN]</title><link>https://jrcampo.com/posts/first-post/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2022 20:03:28 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://jrcampo.com/posts/first-post/</guid><description>¿What is Shodan? 🕵️‍♂️ Shodan is a search engine which uses a database of billions of publicly available IP addresses from a large number of systems, specially IoT devices. It can find anything that connects directly to te internet and if its devices aren&amp;rsquo;t protected, so can tell everything people with bad intentions need to know to break into your network.
In this case, a Python script was developed to perform search automation of desired queries on Shodan.</description></item></channel></rss>